## ASHLEY E. NGUYEN smashflashtech@gmail.com

### FULL-SCACK ENGINEER

Los Angeles, CA

www.smashflashtech.com

(510)449-6706

#### SKILLS

Javascript | HTML5
CSS3 | BOOTSTrap | EJS
REACT | NODE.JS
EXPRESS | SEQUELIZE
POSTGRESSOL | FLASK
SOL ALCHEMY | PYTHON
GIT/GITHUB

## SUMMARY

Behavior analyst pivoting from 12 years of experience collecting and analyzing data and making data-driven decisions to solve problems, implement solutions, and audit success in the context of Human and Autism Services and graduate level education. Seeking an opportunity to apply these skills in the tech industry by building applications that produce measurable improvement in performance and quality of life.

### **PROJECTS**

### Virtual Beer Pong

HTML | CSS | JAVASCRIPT

# Automated Stimulus Display and Data Collection

REACT | SQL ALCHEMY FLASK | PYCHON

#### **Leafy Ledget**

EXPRESS | EJS NODE.JS | POSCGRES SOL

### certificates

GENERAL ASSEMBLY LOS ANGELES (REMOCE) December 2020 Software Engineering

### EDUCATION

THE CHICAGO SCHOOL
OF Professional
PSYCHOLOGY
LOS ANGELES, CA

#### Ph.D. Psychology, Behavior Analysis Specialization

August 2017 - Present GPA: 4.0

#### M.S. Applied Behavior Analysis

October 2015

UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA, BERKELEY **B.A. Psychology** May 2008

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## The Chicago School of Professional Psychology Adjunct Faculty

Los Angeles & Irvine, CA

August 2018 - October 2020

- O Established curriculum and associated experiential activities for master level course now used across three campuses.
- O Lead classroom of graduate level students in instruction, discussion, and hands on application of behavioral technologies across several Practicum topics with 100% pass rate.

#### **Curriculum Development Colaborator**

Chicago, IL (Remote)

August 2019 - April 2020

- O Developed curriculum and associated experiential activities for bachelor level course for remote online instruction.
- O Audited course materials for final publication ensuring curriculum met educational standards and certification board requirements leading to successful course publication by Fall 2020 semester.

## Easterseals Southern California Regional Trainer

Southern California Counties

May 2017 - September 2017

- O Analyzed complex skills and developed standardized training protocols enabling quality assurance competency checks.
- O Trained staff in crisis management and behavioral technologies using research-based methods leading to 100% pass rate.

#### Program Manager

Los Angeles, CA

June 2016 - May 2017

- Supervised staff performance, provided training, assessed morale, and coordinated team building meetings leading to 100% retention of direct supervisees.
- O Evaluated data, summarized results, and recommended treatment options to stakeholders leading to continuation, termination, or graduation of services.

## Working with Autism, Inc. Behavior Intervention Implementer

Los Angeles, CA

January 2012 - February 2016

- Implemented protocols for skill acquisition, problem behavior reduction, and crisis management to increase contact with valuable resources crucial for children with autism.
- O Communicated with clients' interdisciplinary team and parents resulting in continuity of client services across teams and settings.